inbusiness.com 2016-12-13

# Privacy Policy | AllBusiness.com

**Privacy Policy**

**_Updated 9/10/12_**

This privacy policy explains what information is collected when you use our Web site (the “Site”), applications, content and services of AllBusiness.com and its affiliated properties (“AllBusiness”), why this information is collected, and how we use it. When you use our Site, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

**Your AllBusiness Information**

AllBusiness is provided byE-PersonalFinance.com, Inc. and its affiliates (“we”, “our” or “us”). Your AllBusiness information consists of personally identifiable information collected or received about you when you make purchases from us, when you register with us, when you set up profiles to share with others, when you interact with other users on our site, or when you log in to our site as a registered user and interact with our products and services. Your AllBusiness information may include, among other things: (a) registration-related information (such as name, address, telephone and fax numbers, email address); (b) member profile about yourself that you can share with others; (c) a profile on your business or your profession that you desire to share with others, (d) transaction-related information (such as credit card or other preferred means of payment, or a history of products purchased through us); (e) information about your visits to AllBusiness or our other web sites, pages and services; (f) your responses to our offerings and advertisements; (g) information about the features or offerings you use from us; (h) your billing and shipping information; (i) customer service information;  (j) information placed on message boards or forums; and (k) other information specifically related to your use of a particular AllBusiness feature or offering. 

Your information may be supplemented with additional information from other companies such as, for example, publicly available information and other information that we may append or match to your information.

When you register with us, sign up for an application or service, become a member of a company profile or make recommendations on the service, we use certain information we collect from you to set up a profile on your behalf to share with others, and which information will be available by search to help you promote your business or profession. After you register with AllBusiness, you may provide additional member information about yourself (member profile, company profile) and add company profile information about your business. Such member and company profiles could include a description of your services or products, location, web presence and more.

We may offer you services to send invitations via AllBusiness or email addresses if they are not AllBusiness users in order to connect with others on AllBusiness. The names and email addresses of people whom you invite will be used to send your invitations and reminders as well as to allow us to help expand your network. You understand and agree that when you send an invitation to connect to another user, that user will have access to your email address because it is displayed in the invitation. Your connections will also have access to your email address. You should not invite anyone you do not know and trust to connect with you.

By providing information to us for the purposes of creating your AllBusiness account, interacting with our services and features, or adding any additional details to your profile, you understand and agree that we may process information about you and make information about you available to others. In addition, if you post any information about yourself on areas of AllBusiness that are publicly accessible, such as message boards or forums, you understand and agree that such information will be available to others. 

**How AllBusiness Information Is Used**

Your AllBusiness information is used, among other ways, to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by us; to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of our services; to share information about you and your business; to communicate with other users and business contacts; and, to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest or relevance to you.

We may share your information with affiliates, partners, agents or other parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you and/or for marketing purposes. Since AllBusiness is design to help companies and business professionals network with others, AllBusiness is designed so that certain information about you and your business is available to others on AllBusiness and via search engines, including, your name and location of your business, and to help you communicate with companies and business professionals.

The contents of your online communications, as well as other information about you as a AllBusiness user, may also be accessed and disclosed in response to, among other things: (a)to governmental requests or legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena), (b) in other circumstances in which we believe that a crime has been or is being committed by a user or that an emergency exists that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person; or, (c) for us to render the services we provide.

In the event that our ownership may change as a result of a merger or acquisition by another company, your AllBusiness information may be transferred in connection with such merger or acquisition.

You may request that we modify or delete information in your business profile by [contacting us](http://experts.allbusiness.com/contact-us "Contact Us"). We do not guarantee that such changes will be made or when such changes will be made.

**Cookies, Advertising Networks**

We may place “cookies” on your Web browser. Cookies are small pieces of information or text files that a Web site sends to your computer for record-keeping purposes, which information is stored in a file on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies make Web-surfing and browsing easier for you by saving your preferences so that we can use the saved information to facilitate and improve your use of AllBusiness. Please note that you will not be able to access and use all of 

our features if you delete or refuse to accept cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set certain personalized preferences, and/or you may have difficulty completing transactions on AllBusiness. 

Also, we, and certain third party companies under agreement with us, may deploy cookies, pixel tags, web beacons or similar technologies to collect and assemble non-personal, demographic, behavioral and technical information about the use of AllBusiness from our users in order to group such users that share a common interest into general interest categories (collectively, “Audience Segment Cookies”). Such Audience Segment Cookies, which do not identify you personally, may be placed when you access AllBusiness, share content from AllBusiness, when advertisements are presented on AllBusiness, and/or when you respond to advertisements or other offerings on AllBusiness. We and these third party companies may use such non-personally identifiable information in combination with your visits to AllBusiness and other sites in order to present advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you, to measure the effectiveness of AllBusiness and advertisements, and to help predict the characteristics and preferences of our audiences and the audiences of our third party companies. We may share certain information about you as a user that is not personally identified to you (such as, for example, user industry and position) with certain advertising network providers in order to help them deliver more relevant advertisements through their ad networks. The use of cookies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. 

**Security**

We make available a secure page for entering sensitive information, protected by industry-standard SSL encryption technology. This technology encrypts your information prior to transmitting it over the Internet.

While we have established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of you AllBusiness information, we cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, in the event of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or our policies).

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites that have a link on our Web site, are subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Terms of Use Agreement**

Use of this site is subject to our Terms of Use Agreement.

**Questions**

If you have further questions or concerns that have not been addressed in this statement, please send your inquiries to: [contacting us](http://experts.allbusiness.com/contact-us "Contact Us"). Please be sure to include your name, email address, and daytime phone number in case we wish to contact you.

*********
